Contact

4321 Hawks Lookout Ln 5758255399 (Mobile) tabitha.l.leonard14@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/tabitha-leonard-76b743105 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Figma

Customer Service

User Interviews

Certifications

Notary Public

Tabitha Leonard

UI Design Student

Greater Colorado Springs Area

Summary

Customer-focused professional with 10+ years of experience providing expert care in a fast-paced environment. Exceptional relationship building abilities to cultivate positive rapport among clients, staff and management. Highly-developed communicator with outstanding capabilities in complex problem-solving and conflict resolution.

Experience

Student at CareerFoundry
Student
March 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Intervention INC
Case Manager
January 2020 - October 2020 (10 months)
Pueblo, Colorado Area

Maintain an accurate and complete case file for each client on caseload.

Develop individualized case plans for client supervision purposes and monitor progression

Meet with and explain verbally to the client, their case plan to ensure that the client understands his/her responsibilities, meet regularly to assess progress Encourage pro-social behavior, utilize positive behavior change techniques Assess and collect fees related to probation services

Enter client data, progress and meeting notes into computer database Monitor drug and alcohol tests and same sex urine screens as required. Perform assessments/reassessments as required.

State of Colorado
Deputy Probation Officer
August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

Commerce City

Manages an assigned caseload of clients referred by a Court to monitor compliance with court-ordered terms and conditions of probation.

Page 1 of 4

Establishes and maintains a case file on each client including visits to home, workplace, and relevant sites in the community to document compliance with terms and conditions of probation.

Coordinates with various agencies and apprises of client contract obligations; provides copies of documentation, orders and related materials.

Prepares referrals for mental health, counseling, substance abuse, or other evaluations and treatments and monitors attendance at and progress of treatment.

Receives and reviews monthly or other periodic reports from treatment providers on offenders and takes appropriate remedial actions as necessary. Prepares affidavits, motions and orders, warrants of arrest and other legal documents.

Recommends further conditions, initiates affidavit to revoke, or petitions for termination of probation.

Medical Alternatives Clinics Master Scheduler April 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 4 months) Colorado springs

Maintains proficiency in all clerical operations roles to govern accuracy in registration, scheduling, and check out prescribed workflows.

Lead Meetings

Remain proficient and up to date on role responsibilities

Acts as mentor and trainer for front line clerical teams

First responder to investigate patient concerns and maintain customer focused communication

Schedules and drives daily workflow for proficient operational support of the clinic

Advance America Customer Service Representative May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year)

Colorado Springs, Colorado

Prepare forms or agreements to complete sales. Meet with applicants to obtain information for loan applications and to answer questions about the process. Handle customer complaints and take appropriate action to resolve them. Approve loans within state specified limits. Maintain current knowledge of credit regulations. Contact borrowers with delinquent accounts to obtain payment in full or to negotiate repayment plans. Receive payments and post amounts paid to customer accounts. Answer customer questions regarding

problems with their accounts. Confer with customers by telephone or in person to determine reasons for overdue payments and to review the terms of sales, service, or credit contracts.

Progressive Insurance Insurance Agent August 2016 - May 2017 (10 months)

Colorado Springs, Colorado

Customize insurance programs to suit individual customers, often covering a variety of risks. Calculate premiums and establish payment method. Explain features, advantages and disadvantages of various policies to promote sale of insurance plans. Attend meetings, seminars and programs to learn about new products and services, learn new skills, and receive technical assistance in developing new accounts. Calculated quotes, educated potential clients on insurance options, and established payment method.

Firstsource Customer Service Representative October 2015 - August 2016 (11 months)

Colorado Springs, Colorado

Processed credit card payments, responded to inquiries, and resolved issues Addressed customer complaints and escalated calls to proper tier. Manually calculated premium rates and established payment method for polices once they had been issued Promptly handled customer service inquiries, complaints, and service requests from policyholders Handled an extremely high call volume. Resolves product or service problems by clarifying the customer's complaint; determining the cause of the problem; selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem; expediting correction or adjustment; following up to ensure resolution. Reviewed insurance claims with members over the phone. Maintains customer records by updating account information.

Education

CareerFoundry

Certificate in UI Design, UI Design · (April 2021 - March 2022)

Eastern New Mexico University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Criminal Justice/Sociology · (2010 - 2019)

Eastern New Mexico University

Associate's Degree, General Studies · (2010 - 2015)